http://www.portsmouthgolfcentre.co.uk/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Privacy Policyadmin2020-07-20T12:58:47+00:00Who we areOur website address is: https://portsmouthgolfcentre.co.uk.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWho we share your data withHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Your contact informationAdditional informationHow we protect your dataWhat data breach procedures we have in placeWhat third parties we receive data fromWhat automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataIndustry regulatory disclosure requirements
Gift Cards
Gift Cards are available in multiples of £10, £20 or £50 denominations and come with a selection of Gift Cards and envelopes. They are valid for 24 months, and can be spent in the Pro Shop, Range or on Golf Lessons.
Buy Now	Get the latest
Price Match
We aim to offer you the best value possible, on service, our specialist knowledge of our product range and on price. Click to find out more...
Our Shop	Please get in touch if you have a queryLorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua enim ad mi nim g elit
023 9266 4549
enquiries@portsmouthgolfcentre.co.uk
Your name
Your number
Your email
What do you require?
---Golf lessonsCustom fittingOther
Your message
Find Us:Portsmouth Golf Centre,Burrfields Road,Portsmouth,Hampshire,PO3 5HHContact Us: 023 9266 4549 enquiries@portsmouthgolfcentre.co.ukTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyOpening HoursMonday – Friday: 8am – 10pm all year.Saturday: (April – October) 9am – 8pmSaturday: (Nov – March) 9am – 6pmSunday: (April – Sept) 9am – 8pmSunday: (Oct – March) 9am – 6pmBank Holidays: 9am – 8pm
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
Youtube
Company No. 04540852 | Copyright © 2020 Portsmouth Golf centreWebsite designed by Fifteen
Toggle Sliding Bar AreaDriving RangeCustom FittingLessonsThe TeamGolf LessonsGroup LessonsJunior LessonsShopWho We StockGolf CourseLadies GolfJunior GolfGift CardsNews/BlogTestimonialsVideo WallContact
View Cart
Checkout
Continue Shopping
